so my girlfriend is she's white good
okay so the thing is I'm just figuring
out how you feel about it anyways okay
so so diverse in here anyways let's keep
it moving
this is such an eclectic crowd I feel
like half of you I could talk to you
about Facebook and snapchat and I feel
like the rest of you waiting for the
rack back to show up love Sammy Davis
the Candyman can dance tonight Oh what
does he talk anyways reference was a
little old for some of the people some
people like who's the rat back boy
what's up Jack what is that snap face
what is that what I hate what someone
older messes it up on person I was on
that face chat you like you know the
name of it you have an account do you
have an account all the people try to
diss you but then they want you to set
up up how do I had friends you like get
away from me you didn't like it a minute
ago
how do I have French writing all over
your wall ridiculous stuff man is coming
we want to make sure you're here to see
Nana this year you're like can you not
write that on my wall please can you not
do that how about that how about you
just put it in a message I did I'd
message it to you oh my wall forget it
it's gonna block you don't act like you
block some of your family like I don't
even want to do this
I don't block them on following them
because I can't take it anymore right
you're like negative people in real life
but on Facebook they're like everybody
loves everybody you're like in real life
you're the worst person that I know the
dark cloud over you all the time but on
Facebook right there's so all the joys
of the world okay so anyways the girl
the girl I'm with she her family that's
to go to Jersey Shore yeah I told you I
live in Boston so she like her friend
likes to go to church so it's a big
vacation destination we all go to LPI
Long Beach Island it's crazy
Beach time it's everybody's on the beach
so I thought I was gonna be nuts I
thought it's gonna be a party no okay
here's what happens we go rent this
house for a week and whole family and
they wake up at like 6:00 in the morning
right and they drag out all the stuff
out of the house and they bring it to
the beach couches chairs cancer food
sandwiches whoops my mom's like you got
a bookie gonna need a book honey you got
it look he gonna need a book or you got
a book he gonna really need a book you
got a book I was like why do I need a
book she said because we're gonna be
here all day
I had no idea they were all just gonna
sit on the beach and cook in the Sun and
then they all just flipped like little
rotisserie chickens and they just keep
going
and at one point our mom looked at me
she was like are you having a good time
honey I was like yeah I'm having a good
time because I'm respectful but I wasn't
having a good time I wanted to be like
what do you want me to do lay on my back
at 10:00 the bottoms of my hands and my
feet I'm Tara already
how long are we gonna stay here
[Music]
her dad by the third day her dad's
always peeling from his forehead he's
peeling from his nose like I don't know
how I got partnership like really you
don't know you got furnace yet
what happened to the Sun trick you this
year did it somehow hide behind the moon
and it just popped out like burn baby
burn jump back behind the moon and head
we leave her brother always takes his
little pasty arm and he puts it like
next to my arm pray like the second days
like look at me brah Moustakas you home
who's back in here
[Music]
I really is not you're not scared you
would be if you woke up one morning
that's just the right side of your face
was my complexion as a white you blac
[Music]
one of the days I'm sitting there what
everybody I said give me 250 putting on
this unbox it give me 250 my girl I'm
putting on the 50 whatever he starts
laughing her brother slap he's like why
you put our sentence great I'm like why
are you laughing because you're putting
on sunblock I was like yeah why you
laughing it goes cuz you don't eat it I
was like yes I do need him he was like
why I said because a man of me that's
why what do you mean why
this is skin what do you thinking what
do you mean why if I relax I didn't
think you knew that I grew up thinking
black it would it meets them scream I
was like that's the thing you grew up
learning he was like I didn't know
simulated into my brain somehow not
racist clearly I'm hanging out with you
right now so he's like I didn't know ho
you don't mess up as I look at your
faces I feel like you're looking at me
like that's a problem black people need
sunscreen what is wrong with you
what do you think happened to Ponca
Freeman space
all those chocolate chips on his face
that's from his son
it's not genetic it was in a sodium
touchscreen watch my entire special for
99 cents oh just watch more clips check
out more clips click one of them you got
to check it out now if I were you I'd
probably click the $0.99 one cuz that
goes right into my pocket click one
click it click it click lick lick lick
lick lick lick lick lick lick lick lick
okay